const quiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What data structure processes elements adhering to the FIFO principle?",
    answer: "Queue"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "The space between two adjacent grid lines (row or column) is called grid ...",
    answer: "Track"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the term for a JavaScript function that is passed as an argument to another function?",
    answer: "Callback"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What term is used to describe a technique in CSS where a background image moves at a different speed than the foreground content during scrolling?",
    answer: "Parallax"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the term for a combination of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that is packaged for easy distribution and reuse?",
    answer: "Widget"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What HTML5 element is used to draw graphics, animations, and other visual elements on a webpage?",
    answer: "Canvas"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Question 7?",
    answer: "Answer7"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Question 8?",
    answer: "Answer8"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Question 9?",
    answer: "Answer9"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Question 10?",
    answer: "Answer10"
  },
];

export default quiz;